- [Instructor] Now let's work on the get end point,
which will allow us to get all of our players.
So we're going to be working on the same files for a while.
So playerController and soccerRoutes.
So I'm going to open those two files
and just close my Explorer.
So basically the next one that we need
to do in the playerControllers is the get player.
So we're going to basically do a function
that will be called getPlayers.
So we can query the database and get all of our players.
So we're going to use, again, the async approach
with our request, response.
And then let's go ahead
and try to do this.
And then we can actually copy the exact same code here.
If there's an error, catch the error, right?
So, okay, so in the try we're going
to create an array
that will have whatever players we have inside
of our database.
So we're going to use the find command,
and we're not going to pass anything in that find command.
And then we're going to do the response with the players
that we get.
As simple as this.
There's no fluff.
That's basically all that we need
for that controller.
So now we're going to need to pass that controller inside
of the route so we can execute it
with the particular endpoint
that we're going to create for that.
So let's go ahead
and make sure we have a comma, getPlayers.
And then we're going to create a get endpoint,
which will use the same player.
So we're going to use the get method with the same endpoint,
which is players,
and pass the controller getPlayers.
And this is how simple it gets.
So let's just make sure we put some notes here,
get endpoint, if you want to take some notes.
Is this is your first time to do a full MERN application,
putting some notes down might actually be a good idea
just to give you an idea
of what you can do afterwards
when you build your own application.
So just as a refresher,
we're importing the playerController that we just created.
We're exporting it here.
We're basically going
into the Mongo database using mongos
and trying to find all the players.
And then basically returning the response with the array
of players that we have.
Otherwise give an error.
And then we're using this route with a get method
to get all the players.
So what I'm going to do is save this,
'cause this is basically our code.
Want to make sure our server is still running.
Yep, and there's no error.
I'm just going to minimize this.
And the first thing I'm going to do is go inside Postman here,
and I'm going to create a bunch of other players
with the same data here.
So I'm going to create Manuello, Henrietto
and then change this to 5 so I have different data,
and maybe have another key here
where it could be tactical.
And then put a one.
And then send this, get a response back.
We have another player.
And I'm going to again do another one here.
So Henri, Manuel,
I'm going to reverse my first name, last name,
change me2@me.com
and put a 6 here.
And just send this again.
So basically now if we remove all these items,
'cause we don't need anything in the body
to do a get request,
and we do a get request
with the player's endpoint, same endpoint,
we're going to have an array of responses here.
And if you want to check even further,
you can go into Studio 3T, do another search,
and you'll see that we have three different players, right?
So you know that everything is working
as it should based on these tests.
So once we actually use the get endpoint from the frontend,
which is going to be the React application,
we're going to get this data returned to us as a JSON.
So we got our get endpoint, let's move on.